{
  "cultures": [
    {
      "name": "Chinese",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionNum": 1,
          "question": "How do you say 'Hello' in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Nihao", "Xiexie", "Zao"],
          "correctAnswer": "Nihao"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 2,
          "question": "How do you say 'Thank you' in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Shi", "Xiexie", "Wo jiao"],
          "correctAnswer": "Xiexie"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 3,
          "question": "What does 'Bù kèqì' mean in Chinese?",
          "options": ["You're Welcome", "Good Morning", "My name is..."],
          "correctAnswer": "You're welcome"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 4,
          "question": "How do you say 'Good morning' in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Hao", "Zao", "Wan an"],
          "correctAnswer": "Zao"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 5,
          "question": "What does 'Wǎn ān' mean in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Good night", "Do not stick your chopstick perpendicularly on rice"],
          "correctAnswer": "Good night"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 6,
          "question": "How do you say 'My name is…' in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Shi", "Wo jiao", "Bu Shi"],
          "correctAnswer": "Wo jiao"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 7,
          "question": "What does 'Shì' mean in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Yes", "No", "Good"],
          "correctAnswer": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 8,
          "question": "What does 'Bù shì' mean in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Yes", "No", "Good"],
          "correctAnswer": "No"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 9,
          "question": "What does 'Hǎo' mean in Chinese?",
          "options": ["Yes", "Good", "Do shake hands when you meet someone for the first time"],
          "correctAnswer": "Good"
        },
        {
          "questionNum": 10,
          "question": "What is a cultural etiquette in Chinese dining?",
          "options": ["Do not stick your chopstick perpendicularly on rice", "Do arrive on time", "Remove your shoes before entering someone's home or certain indoor spaces"]
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
